{
    "subject": "resource/London_Biggin_Hill_Airport",
    "predicate": "ontology/runwaySurface",
    "object": "Asphalt",
    "human_readable": "The runway surface of London Biggin Hill Airport is Asphalt.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.952009916305542,
            "question": "London Biggin Hill Airport has a runway surface of what material?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8950172066688538,
            "question": "What type of surface covers the runway at London Biggin Hill Airport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8942887187004089,
            "question": "Is the runway surface at London Biggin Hill Airport made of concrete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7881614565849304,
            "question": "What material is used for the runway at London Biggin Hill Airport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7531202435493469,
            "question": "Is the runway at London Biggin Hill Airport made of a durable material?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7322404980659485,
            "question": "What is the composition of the runway at London Biggin Hill Airport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7156735062599182,
            "question": "What type of surface would airplanes land on at London Biggin Hill Airport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6724891662597656,
            "question": "Which material makes up the landing strip at London Biggin Hill Airport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6315099596977234,
            "question": "What is the primary material used for the runway at Biggin Hill Airport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41387495398521423,
            "question": "Is Asphalt a common material used for airport runways?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The runway surface of London Biggin Hill Airport is Asphalt.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2864_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary material used for the runway at Biggin Hill Airport?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2864_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which material makes up the landing strip at London Biggin Hill Airport?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2864_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of surface would airplanes land on at London Biggin Hill Airport?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2864_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2864_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer to the query \"The runway surface of London Biggin Hill Airport is Asphalt.\" would be:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThis is because while one of the runways (03L/21R) has an asphalt/concrete surface, another runway (11L/29R) has an asphalt surface, and a third runway (1,802 m x 45 m) is mentioned as having an asphalt/concrete surface. Therefore, it's not accurate to say that \"The runway surface of London Biggin Hill Airport is Asphalt.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the runway surfaces at Biggin Hill Airport, including that one of the runways (03L/21R) has an asphalt and asphalt/concrete surface. Therefore, the statement \"The runway surface of London Biggin Hill Airport is Asphalt\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The runway surface information contradicts with the provided details under point 1.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}